(Today, the King of Living Alone)
"The King of Living Alone."
(Gyeong Hye is busy going somewhere in the morning.)
You're keeping busy in the morning.
Right. Whoever walks that fast is bound to be diligent.
Right.
Hello.
I've already been living alone for half a year now.
I'm actor Park Gyeong Hye. Nice to see you again.
She's so cheerful.
(She's living in a tiny 19.8m² studio.)
It's been a while.
(She was a newbie at living alone who moved out 4 months ago.)
(I'll take your order up here.)
(She's a part-timer at night.)
That's the cool cafe.
(She's so cute. This is the reality of living alone.)
(I love seeing how hardworking she is.)
Actually, after sharing my day-to-day life...
in this studio on the show,
so many people expressed...
- their support for me. - Right.
Hye Soo, Tae Hyun, In Na,
and other seniors whom I worked with...
called and texted me to express their support.
When I ran into people on the streets,
so many of them wished me good luck for my solo life.
That's why I'm more willing to do things on my own...
even if I end up making mistakes and redoing them.
That's been my attitude.
So there are more things I can handle on my own now.
That's what I can tell you about myself now.
Actually, I passed by the cafe you worked at to see you.
- Really? - But you weren't there.
- I did too. - You too?
- Really? - I always check when I pass by.
So many people came to the cafe to show their support.
I've received so many letters as well.
I see. A lot of people expressed their support.
- People came to show their support. - I see.
Yes. I wanted to thank everyone who came to show their support.
(While carrying a big shopping bag, )
(she's going somewhere alone.)
Where is she going?
Aren't you her?
- The actress? - I am.
- You are? - She recognized you right away.
- She's shy. She whispered. - Thank you.
I remember you.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
- Bye. - Bye.
Bye.
(Chuckling)
What a proud moment.
People love it when they see you on the streets, right?
- Yes. I'm grateful for that. - Right.
The moment you're recognized as an actress,
you become a national star.
That's nice.
(She's happily heading somewhere.)
(She has arrived...)
(at a community service center?)
Hello.
(She stops in front of a huge machine upon entering.)
Where did you go with the plastic bottles?
(She grabs a plastic bottle.)
(Inserting)
(She keeps on putting them into the machine.)
What's she doing?
You can trade in the bottles there.
You just have to remove the label sheets around the bottles.
(That's right.)
What will she get in return?
Actually, I didn't know about this when I went here before.
Then I noticed this huge machine one day.
I wondered what it was and asked them about it.
When I put in the plastic bottles, they give me points in return.
And they said I could use the points like cash.
- Really? - So I got interested.
Let me explain. We're bound to use plastic bottles...
when we're filming.
So I suddenly remembered all the plastic bottles on set.
I was like, "That's all money."
Did you take all of them with you?
After finding out about the machine,
I shared this information on set.
Everyone drinks water...
- from plastic bottles on set. - Yes.
They said, "Do you want to take them, Gyeong Hye?"
So I've been taking a lot of them.
(She's collecting a lot of plastic bottles thanks to them.)
I'll drink up the water and give it to you.
- Thank you so much. - I'll drink three bottles today.
- Seriously. Today? - You can take them.
- That's great. - I'll drink three bottles of it.
It's a promise.
There are so many benefits from the community service centers.
- They also offer a lot of classes. - Yes.
- Educational programs. - Yes. They offer such programs.
In the centers?
Do you work at the center? How come you know everything?
My community service center is nearby.
- I borrowed tools from the center. - Right.
You didn't pass the civil service exam, right?
(He continues to suspect Dae Ho.)
I've been feeling insecure about my career lately.
(I've been feeling insecure about my career lately.)
I've been insecure. So I'm going to work hard.
You know everything civil servants would know.
You see so many interesting programs when you look around the center.
You seem like a different person.
(Popping it into the machine)
- I see. One by one? - Yes. It's like a vending machine.
They give me 100 points per bottle.
That's one cent.
One cent?
(She keeps on putting in the bottles.)
(Points earned: 2,900 points)
- Did you already hit the limit? - Right.
I found out for the first time that day.
I could only bring in 30 bottles a day...
- It can't go over 30? - because...
To keep anyone from hogging it.
- That's true. - To make sure no one hogs it.
- If persistent people try this, - Right.
They could make 600,000 dollars.
- Right. - That's so true. People...
- If this becomes their thing... - It's not even about the money.
- They'll be there all day long. - Right.
That's 3,000 points.
(She saved 3,000 points today.)
- You accumulated quite a lot. - Yes.
- Right. - She has 4,540 points.
You can use these points to buy a lot of things.
Gosh, I need double the points.
The thing is, I shop at Daiso a lot.
I thought it'd feel great to use the points at Daiso.
- I earned these points. - Right.
I was happy when I found out...
I could use the points there.
(After checking her points...)
Gosh, I learned a new thing from her.
I'd go there often if I lived close to the center.
(Instead of heading home, Gyeong Hye gets in the car.)
- What? - My gosh.
Where is she going now? She's super busy.
(You said)
(I was the only one you loved)
(Swaying)
(Suddenly getting sad)
(She nails every genre of music in the car.)
(She's driving somewhere in a good mood.)
Wait. That's the way to the cafe where you work at.
- She must be going there to work. - To work?
(Humming)
Look at her, carrying all that stuff.
(Is she making haste to get to work?)
(Chuckling)
(Laughing)
- Right. That's the cafe. - She's going there to work.
- Yes. That's the cafe. What? - What?
(Staring)
(A construction site?)
The cafe closed down.
- The cafe closed down. - Really?
The cafe wasn't there anymore.
(She worked at the cafe while building her acting career.)
(She had worked there for 2 years.)
- That was a hip cafe. - Enjoy.
Wait. My old favorite spot is gone now?
Right. You have memories about this place.
(Her lovely place of work for the past 2 years...)
(is under renovation.)
- Why all of a sudden? - What?
Why did it close down?
The thing is, the owner of the cafe...
gave birth to this beautiful baby.
As a new parent, she wouldn't be able to...
manage the cafe like she used to, realistically speaking.
So we all worked together on its last day, May 12.
Then I said goodbye to the cafe.
(Gyeong Hye recorded her last day at the cafe.)
(She spent 2 years working at this cafe.)
I always drank there.
- Right. The window seat, right? - Yes, that's it.
(Extracting the last cup of coffee before closing)
I was extracting coffee on my last day.
I teared up a bit too.
That must feel weird.
- Their last shift? - Yes, it's their last shift.
It's so sad because...
Why am I choking up?
You worked there for two years.
- That must feel weird. - Of course.
Working at the cafe was one thing. But I had gotten close...
- to the other workers. - You have a lot of memories.
Right. I was so used to seeing them at work.
The thought of not being able to...
- see them again... - Right.
- made me sad. - Yes.
I picked the worst day to go back to the cafe because...
There used to be a sign.
But they switched the doors for the new business that day.
- It's sadder. - Right. I guess...
that made me feel more emotional.
(A lot has changed already.)
(Her former place of work changed a lot.)
I'm sad about the news too.
(She can't seem to walk away from the cafe.)
(Sighing)
- Hello, sir. - Hello.
It's been a while.
Hello. Oh, hi, there.
Actually, the restaurant owner made great meals and snacks for us.
He runs a taco restaurant.
I dropped by to give him some rice cakes...
and have a delicious taco as an early lunch.
I also wanted to say goodbye one last time.
Actually, I went there to tell him I'd stop by often.
I'm about to tear up.
This is the first time I saw the construction work.
- Really? - The cafe... Yes.
"This is my new place of work."
She's going to steal the part-timer's job.
- I won't leave the restaurant. - Right.
That's the most familiar spot if there's any.
- My gosh. - Right.
Oh, right. This is nothing big.
You can have them with your staff.
- Really? - I brought rice cakes and sikhye.
- Really? - They're really tasty.
I order them for myself too.
- How kind. - She's so good at sharing.
I wanted you to try some too.
- Thank you. We'll enjoy them. - Don't mention it.
Okay.
- That's my order. Thank you. - Sure.
- It won't take long. - Okay.
Doesn't it feel a bit empty with the cafe gone now?
The cafe and our restaurant seemed to make a good team.
- Right. - Your restaurant helped a lot.
Customers came to the cafe...
- after having a meal here. - Right.
So we were grateful too.
We feel the same way.
- You want coffee after the taco. - Yes.
- Right. - They make a good combo.
We had to say goodbye to each other out of the blue.
- Here's your drink. - Thank you.
Sure.
Oh, my. Sir.
Gosh, look at her reaction.
She didn't even look at it.
You can't have guacamole without nachos.
You always take such good care of me when I come here to eat.
- Thank you for the food. - Sure.
- I didn't order that. - Oh, my.
- That looks good. - It was on the house.
- It was on the house. - Thank you.
(Crunchy)
(Humming)
I'm in trouble.
This tastes so good.
(Humming)
I love guacamole.
- It's so good. - Yes.
That does look good.
(She takes a big bite of the taco.)
(This is what I'm talking about.)
- It's so good. - Thank you.
Are you still working part-time?
- The cafe closed down. - Right. Are you unemployed now?
(Joking)
You don't need a part-timer, do you?
Give me your resume.
She asked him right away.
I'd have to do an interview, right?
Working at a taco place suits you too.
Are you still looking for a part-time job?
Right now, I'm working on a project with my acting...
- which I'm grateful for. - Right.
But I'm worried that...
I feel quite down when I'm not working on any project.
But when I keep working, I get a sense of achievement...
and can feel that I'm using my energy for something.
So when I'm between projects again,
having a part-time job...
- is really helpful. - Right.
- That's great. - It's good to have work.
(Taking a bite while feeling gratitude)
- Seriously. It's so good. - Gosh, she's eating with gusto.
This is nice. You're eating taco, and he's eating the rice cakes.
(The heartwarming scene of sharing food)
This is sad.
I'll come by often to eat here.
- Everyone's sad. - It was nice to see you around.
Right.
We saw each other quite often when I worked at the cafe.
- It feels like I'm a local here. - At first, I didn't recognize you.
- Right. - "She looks familiar."
I see. Really?
Yes. You were wearing overalls then.
Oh, right.
You love making small talk.
She's like an American.
I was like, "I've seen her somewhere."
But to think that I won't see you guys often...
I'll come back to eat here.
The food was great today.
- Bye. Thank you. - Bye.
You didn't take your card.
Thank you.
- She didn't take her card? - She didn't. She must go back.
I forget to take my card so often.
Nowadays, you have to pay at the machine yourself.
- Right. - You know where I had to go back?
I left my card at Mungyeongsaejae Pass...
- on a weekend. - Oh, no!
- I had to go back there. - What?
- Really? - Yes.
- Why didn't you... - You could've gotten it renewed.
Why did you go back?
I could have gotten it renewed.
(I didn't think of that.)
- That sounds so dumb. - Oh, that...
I told you to call me whenever you had problems.
Why are you telling me that now?
When else could I have told you?
(He learned something new today.)
Thank you. Bye.
The food was great!
(This goodbye)
(Won't be forever)
(Leaving behind the sorrow of parting...)
Let's go.
- She came home. - She came home.
- There. - She's home.
- There's no elevator. - Right. There's no elevator.
(We're in the same boat.)
What?
- My gosh. It looks much better now. - Gosh.
- Yes. He fixed it up. - Oh, him. Yes.
- Let's try this. - He went viral.
Everyone wanted to know who this handsome guy was.
- Really? - He went viral.
See? It's all about our looks.
Appearance is what matters.
Did you just figure that out? We must work hard.
- He only did that. - If you're handsome, you get...
- famous by putting on stickers. - Of course.
- We won't get 300,000 views... - Hey.
Even if we eat the sheets.
- We can't. - Right.
I should run 100km for my marathon.
You should.
(She and Chan Hyeong put the sheets only on the cabinet doors.)
(The whole sink cabinet looks white now.)
It does look much cleaner now.
It changed the vibe of your house completely.
- It looks completely different. - So...
I'm really proud because...
I did the rest by myself.
- Great job. - Really?
- You did a great job. - Right.
Yes. I worked really hard on it. And I did it all by myself.
I was so proud of finishing this job...
- all by myself. - It's a proud moment.
That's why you're the king of living alone now.
You're the king of living alone.
- It looks like a new sink cabinet. - Yes.
(Next to the sink cabinet decorated by the king of living alone...)
- What's going on? - What?
- You still haven't finished it. - What?
- I see. But your stuff... - Are you packing?
What's going on? What is this?
(Under the top bunk bed which she set up last time, )
(it's clustered with clothes.)
- I got more stuff as I lived there. - Right.
I started to run out of space to store them.
It turns out I don't have an eye for design.
I have no idea what goes well with what.
I'm not good at matching things up.
So I'm ready for a new challenge to push myself to grow.
(After changing into comfortable clothes...)
(Hopping over)
(She shoves her things into a suitcase as big as her.)
(Adding more things to an already-full suitcase)
(Lugging)
Where is she going now? My gosh.
Where is she going?
- She has so much energy. - Seriously.
Seriously. She has so much stamina.
People like her make good runners.
(Showing interest)
(Shoving the bags into the back seat)
All done.
(Opening up)
The moving boxes?
(She takes out moving boxes from the trunk.)
(Glancing back)
Put in the passcode.
Wait.
- Hello, sir. - "Sir?"
- Are you from a furniture company? - Wait.
- Yes. - A furniture company?
Are you from a furniture company?
- Yes. - Hello.
(She bought another piece of furniture after the bunk bed?)
- Where... - Will you sleep standing up?
There's no spare space.
Well, winter is gone, and summer is here.
I don't have a lot of summer clothes here.
I still have some of my clothes at my parents' house...
because I don't have much space here.
I made a big decision of buying a closet.
I can switch my winter clothes for summer clothes.
I'm going to transition my house from winter to summer.
For this new makeover, this is what I've prepared.
Greed is endless when living alone!
It looks like you and I are quite similar.
You keep changing your house.
(Shaking hands)
I bet she'll bring in sand pretty soon.
(The ultimate house of endless desires, Dae Ho's house)
It still feels like a dream.
Right. It wasn't a dream.
Wait. It's not going in.
(She gets ready to bring more changes to the house.)
(I must get rid of them quickly.)
(Pulling down)
(Quickly disassembling the rack)
She's so quick.
(Going up and down the stairs...)
I should slow down.
(nonstop)
Gosh, no. Thank you.
- You're throwing that out. - Right. Throw it out.
(She's throwing out the furniture she no longer uses.)
(Meanwhile, the new furniture is being brought up.)
It's quite big.
(Quickly running up after him)
Times like this make me feel so bad...
that I live in a building without an elevator.
I feel the same way.
(As soon as she comes back, )
(she opens up the fridge.)
- I'm sorry. The AC isn't working. - No, it's okay.
Would you like some sikhye?
It's nothing compared to your help.
- Gosh, how thoughtful of you. - Right. She must offer drinks.
I'm sorry for making you work in this bad environment.
(Scanning)
Right?
(Crouching down)
(She sits in the corner quietly and observes them.)
(Staring)
(Last time when she set up her bed...)
(You know what I think?)
(I'm living alone for the first time in my life.)
Did you not drink this on purpose?
(She stayed next to him and talked nonstop.)
(Ghost Small Talk had emerged into the studio.)
(I used to install air conditioners for a living before.)
(This kind of customer is the most uncomfortable.)
(Shocked)
(It's nice that you offered him coffee.)
(But I get nervous in case I mess things up.)
You tried to stay out of their sight and stayed quiet.
Look at her hiding there.
(She quietly observes them.)
After hearing that from Ji Hyeon, I started to act more carefully.
I got to hear a different perspective from him.
I mean, he used to be in a similar line of work.
- I realized I missed that. - You could understand his point.
After realizing what I overlooked, I couldn't help...
but be more careful.
Ji Hyeon spared a lot of people the trouble.
(Joking)
(She stays quiet not to bother the workers.)
I want to try that.
She has so many things to say, but her mouth is shut tightly.
- I bet she bit her tongue. - Right.
It's not here.
Do you feel uncomfortable that I'm watching you guys?
Other customers also watch us work.
- It's nice that we get to... - Yes.
Show you the parts you can't see once we assemble everything...
while we work on this.
- Right. - That's great.
(Lightening up)
As you saw earlier, I used to have a rack here.
- But I love to cook. - Yes.
So my clothes started to smell like food.
I see. Right.
I actually have rhinitis too.
- Me too. - Really?
I know effective medicine for rhinitis.
When I ventilate the house,
- pollen comes in. - Right.
- And it'd stick on my clothes. - Yes.
Then pollen and I get locked up in this house.
- So I needed a closet. - There she goes again.
(Ghost Small Talk is emerging out.)
I just carry a nasal spray with me because it gets frustrating.
And you also have to think about dust.
"I shouldn't have responded."
You have to drill it hard. Right?
You must drill it hard and carefully.
They're talking about drilling too?
(Their conversation is flowing smoothly.)
You can call me if you have any questions.
I take calls until 10pm.
You always know the sweetest things to say.
- Me? - Yes.
I need to be kind to my customers.
(They're influenced by her friendly nature.)
I have this injeolmi. It's so good.
This kind of friendly nature is rare these days.
I love that you haven't changed.
(As they have a friendly conversation, )
(the closet is almost done being assembled.)
There.
- It looks neat. - Hey, that looks great.
Right. It looks neat.
(Amazed)
(Gasping)
(All-white interior design gives a modern vibe.)
Your house looks much better with that.
That's just perfect.
(Her house looks much neater.)
We're done.
- Thank you. - We're done. We'll get going now.
Okay. Thank you. Here's your coffee.
- Have some rice cakes too. - Why are you giving us so much?
- Gosh, no. Rice cakes are... - Okay.
All thawed. You can have them now.
We'll have it in the car. Thank you for the coffee.
- Don't mention it. - Thank you.
- Bye. - Bye.
Take care.
(She sees them off to the door.)
(Excited)
Paroma.
- I know the commercial. - Paroma.
- There was a commercial. - What's Paroma?
- Right. - You don't know this commercial?
That's such an old commercial.
She looks so cool.
(Summoning an old memory as she's excited)
I can do the Paroma commercial here.
If you're a bit silly,
you'd forget to pull out your head before closing it.
- Stop talking about Sung Hwan. - No.
You know what? I got you this time.
I was watching you when you said that.
You were looking at me with your left eye.
- Then you turned right afterwards. - You were spot on.
(Glancing at Sung Hwan who's on his left)
(Then he shared what must have come to his mind afterward.)
- My friend did that before. - I'm not that dumb.
- My friend did that once. - Okay.
- My friend... - You looked down on me.
- It'd hit your head. - You're beheading yourself.
(I've been watching you, smartypants.)
(After having fun with the new closet, )
(she wipes the dust.)
Pants.
(She grabs her clothes under the bunk bed.)
It's great to see her clothes going into the closet.
All done. I put away the clothes.
(Rustling)
(Since she's at it, she tries to take down the curtains.)
(I have a good feeling about this.)
I think I can do this. Oh, my.
You're going to do that on your own?
That's a hard job for a woman to handle on her own.
It was my first time trying it.
(Falling)
Wait.
(Flustered)
(She calmly brings down the curtain rod.)
(Even if I end up making mistakes, I should try to do them on my own.)
This is great. Slow down, Gyeong Hye.
(She disassembles the curtain rod on her own.)
She's good.
Here come the blinds at last.
Blinds?
Because my place was incredibly drafty,
I set up long velvet curtains.
But they made the window area damp in summer.
On top of dampness,
- airing the house became a hassle. - That's right.
- I air the house often. - I see.
So I decided to switch to blinds.
- Curtains are so hot in summer. - That's right.
That's right.
(She begins to set up the blinds right away.)
I see that she needs new brackets.
Yes.
(She quickly installs the first bracket.)
The height is just right.
- Oh, my. - My goodness.
(Surprised)
(Drilling)
It's in.
It's becoming so wrinkly.
(She struggled with vinyl wrapping...)
(when she was new to living alone.)
Gosh, Gyeong Hye.
(Now, she easily does things on her own.)
(Focused)
Nice.
(She finishes setting up the brackets.)
You're a good worker.
(Only the blinds remain!)
(Clicking)
(Lifting her leg)
You're doing great.
(Going up)
Hold on.
(Sweating)
Now...
- How are the legs positioned? - What's up with that leg?
(She focuses on the task in an acrobatic pose.)
I'll take showers four times today.
A bit more.
(Clicking)
Let's push it in here.
(The rod goes into the last bracket.)
(She finishes setting up the blinds by herself.)
(Happy)
Let's lower the blinds.
(Lowering)
They go down so suddenly.
- They're pretty. - They're neat.
- They're much better. - They're much better.
(In unison)
Now,
let's close them.
Let's turn off the light quickly.
(Running over)
(Turning off the light)
(The blinds definitely work well.)
- That's good. - They're neat.
- You set them up neatly. - They look pretty.
(I did it on my own!)
Is she that happy?
(Embarrassed)
Do you know what I've realized?
- I'm a worrywart. - That's right.
I found an upside to being a worrywart.
When something goes better than my worry,
I become much happier.
I'm jealous of her ability to be happy about the small things.
When I'm in a bad mood, I call Gyeong Hye.
It uplifts my mood.
- It uplifts your mood? - Yes.
- Thank you so much. - Seriously.
(She set up the blinds on her own.)
(Moved)
(Singing)
I'm excessive, right?
- No. - We love it.
(Not at all!)
(She continues to organize the house.)
(She puts things away in the staircase drawers.)
(Then she changes the bedding.)
I've been using a fleece blanket.
- It must've been hot. - You need a summer blanket.
(She switches to the white summer blanket.)
Come on. Come forward.
(Struggling)
(She vacuums the floor cleanly...)
(and puts the remaining pieces of furniture in their spots.)
(She finishes organizing the house.)
She is good.
Gyeong Hye, it was like playing "Tetris."
Wilson, what do you think?
What do you think?
The house looks so nice.
(Answering her own question)
(Screaming)
(Happy)
(Before the cleanup)
(After the cleanup)
Look at the difference.
- I can't believe it. - "Love House."
It's like "Love House."
Perhaps I'm making a big fuss,
but I feel like the house has gained about 6.6m².
That's right. There is more space.
(After the cleanup)
(Panting)
(It was a fulfilling day!)
She'll sleep well tonight.
For the first time in a while, I sweated a lot that day.
(Drinking)
(Doing things alone isn't easy.)
Shall I lie down for one minute?
(Lying down)
(Let's rest for 1 minute.)
(Getting up)
She actually got up after one minute.
(1 minute is up.)
(After charging her stamina for 1 minute, )
(she washes away her sweat.)
(Feeling refreshed)
(Feeling clean, she heads over to the fridge.)
All right.
(Putting down)
This is such a delicious rice cake.
- Rice cake again? - It's rice cake.
- My goodness. - Do you sell rice cake these days?
It isn't like that. It's my first time eating it.
- Really? - Yes.
- That's right. - She is right.
She just gave it to other people.
(Let's plate it nicely.)
(Knocking)
- That startled me. - What?
(Did someone come to the house?)
Who is it?
Maybe it's her handsome friend.
- Chan Hyeong? Is it him? - Lee Chan Hyeong.
(Opening the door)
Okay. Open your eyes.
- What? - Ta-da.
He is a foreigner.
- That startled me. - Who is it?
It's Justin.
- Justin? - What?
- Justin. - Yes?
- Close your eyes. - Okay.
(A sudden English conversation?)
(Opening the door)
Okay. Open your eyes.
- What? - Ta-da.
He is a foreigner.
Do you only let handsome men into your house?
That man is cool as well.
He is cool.
Ta-da.
He is my guy friend...
and my English teacher, Justin.
He makes English lessons fun...
so that I don't feel like I'm studying.
I've been taking English lessons for about a year.
When I filmed "Escape from Mogadishu,"
- "Escape from Mogadishu." - I became close to the locals.
They asked me,
"Will you come over today as well?"
I wanted to ask them how they were doing...
or which dishes were tasty that day.
I was desperate to talk to them.
My friends who spoke English conversed with them freely,
but I had to wait for the translation.
And I didn't always have an internet connection.
- That's right. - Without an internet connection,
- I couldn't say a word. - You were frustrated.
That's right. I wanted to converse with them.
That experience made me learn English more diligently.
Seriously.
(Justin, welcome to my changed house.)
- Oh, my gosh. - I changed it.
- She is good at English. - She is good at English.
Summer change.
- Summer change? - Yes.
- Different color? - Yes, different color.
- Her pronunciation is good. - It's good indeed.
- You made it? - Yes.
It was green.
- Yes, it was green. - Okay.
How is it?
- Is that your boyfriend? - Yes.
My new roommate.
- Your roommate? What's his name? - Yes.
The name is...
I suddenly forgot.
- I definitely knew it. - What?
- Terrible friend. - No.
What... What is your name?
Seriously.
It wasn't William.
(It wasn't William.)
- What? - I'm disappointed.
Suddenly...
Hasn't that happened to you?
Suddenly, I couldn't remember it.
Wilson.
- It happens. - Wilson isn't very well-known.
That isn't true.
Its name isn't very well-known.
Suddenly, I couldn't remember it.
- I wanted to introduce Wilson. - It does start with "Wil."
- Sit here. - Okay.
- I'll give you something. - Okay.
You speak very naturally.
- Here. - Her English has improved a lot.
And enjoy this.
- Wow, this is nice. - This is my secret place.
And I'll give you something.
- Wait a second, please. - Okay.
- Enjoy this place. - Your English is good.
- Your English has improved a lot. - It has improved a lot?
- People like her learn quickly. - Thank goodness.
We began learning English together.
Did you learn English?
- I forgot about that. - Sung Hwan learned it in the past.
When Sung Hwan and I went abroad together,
- he spoke English. - I spoke English.
Hey, Mr. Guy.
Well...
- "Mr. Guy?" - "Well..."
Hey. Please, Mr. Guy.
One more... Play.
(I give up.)
I'll give you something.
- Wait a second, please. - Okay.
- Enjoy this place. - Okay.
Yes.
(There she goes again.)
Sorry. I don't have a tray.
If I had a tray, more good.
"More good" equals "Better."
He corrected her right away.
Wait.
(She doesn't understand.)
I was busy preparing the snack.
That's my cutting board.
(She picks up a cutting board instead of a tray.)
I hope you don't drop it.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm nervous.
- Gosh. - Don't worry.
I'm not worried. It's about your rug. It's so white and clean.
(Sikhye and rice cake arrive safely.)
(Drink it.)
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Oh, my gosh.
- Justin loves Korean food. - How is it?
- It's so sweet. - Right.
(Proud)
- Did you do your homework? - Yes, teacher.
- Okay. - There is homework as well.
I have a quiz. Do you want me to read the words?
- Do you want to take this quiz? - There are a vocabulary quiz...
and a separate quiz which involves making a sentence with the words.
- It's systematic. - Okay.
Nervous.
That's correct.
Honored. Honor. Honored.
Dedicated.
- Dedicated. - When I say the words out loud...
during the vocabulary quiz,
- Justin corrects my pronunciation. - He corrects it.
So saying the words out loud became a habit.
You prefer saying the words out loud, right?
Chatty people learn English more quickly. Look at Yeong Cheol.
(Fluent)
I 100 percent... I definitely memorized this word.
But I suddenly forgot.
Okay. Then we can go... That's wrong.
Hint, please.
- There is no hint. - Let me try to get a triangle.
Let me try to get a triangle, please.
Just one hint, please.
- No. - No?
It's best when the teacher is strict and on point.
- That's right. - Yes.
- Are you done? - Yes.
Fill in the blank. "I'm a little nervous..."
"because this is my first time speaking English on camera."
That's correct.
Sure. Correct.
"Thank you for helping me. I'm really grateful."
"I'm very excited today."
Correct. "I feel honored."
- She is good. - She will get the perfect score.
"Dedicated person."
"Dedication" is a different word.
- Noun, right? - Yes.
- What's my score? - One, two...
Actually, you did better than I expected.
- Really? - One, two...
Really. Twenty-three.
Twenty-three? Oh, my gosh.
- Gosh. - She is good.
- I... - Today, you're good.
I'm always a good student.
This is weird.
Not weird.
Maybe you should walk over.
- Okay. - "Excuse me."
(Walking over)
Oh, my gosh! Ms. Gyeong Hye!
- Oh, my gosh! Ms. Gyeong Hye! - What?
Ms. Gyeong Hye!
His pronunciation is better than mine.
- It must be a skit. - Yes.
- A skit? - Gosh.
To be honest,
I look up celebrities' English interviews.
I've watched Lee Jung Eun's English interview.
She looked so cool.
She is so cool.
That's right.
(We enjoyed working with Mr. Bong.)
(How knew how to elevate our creativity as actors.)
- It's always... - Her English is good.
Seriously. It became the talk of the town.
"I want to talk about..."
"my movies and characters this fluently."
When I told Justin that,
he suggested doing a skit in which I could explain my character.
So we had an interview skit for this lesson.
- You might go to a film festival. - That's right.
- Yes. - You might get interviewed.
- That'd be great. - Yes.
- I hope that day comes. - How cool.
- It'll come. - Soon.
I'm certain that it'll come.
- I believe in you. - That'd be great.
I'll study English hard.
I met a great teacher.
To this day, the only Japanese I know is what I've told Ito Junji.
I stopped learning then.
- Did you stop learning Japanese? - I stopped.
- Why? - I have no motivation.
- Motivation is important. - Yes.
- You studied hard to meet him. - Yes.
- Thank you. - We're so happy to have you here.
Yes. Thank you.
What do you think of Korean culture being so popular?
What do you think of Korean culture being...
so popular in the world?
It's a difficult question.
- I'm so proud. - Yes.
And...
Apologize. Not "Apologize."
What did you want to say?
Ms. Park Gyeong Hye, focus.
- Focus. - Appre...
- "Grateful?" - Grateful.
- "Appreciate?" - Appreciate.
- Yes. Sure. - Appreciate.
- Appreciate. - It's a difficult word.
- Since it's a professional setting, - That's right.
I need to use fitting words.
It's the advanced version of "Thank you."
It's just...
For this moment.
For.
- Preparing for. - For.
Okay.
Easygoing, positive...
I like "Optimistic."
Okay. Optimistic. Then you can figure this out.
I want to do a good job...
in my current work as an actor.
The thing is,
I can't be certain that the works will be consistent.
But I'm still a rookie at living alone...
who wants to do many things.
I want to learn many things...
and I'm interested in many things.
So while working hard on my part-time jobs...
as well as my main job,
I want to expand my horizon...
as much as I want.
I think I'll need to put a lot of effort...
into my work.
- You're cool. - Thank you.
See off.
- See off. - See off.
Her day is packed.
(Taking out)
Then...
Is she going over what she has learned?
She lives diligently.
That way, I don't forget what I have learned.
- That's right. - Half an hour is enough.
- Otherwise, you forget everything. - You need to go over it that day.
- I know. - That's right.
(Leveling Up Today As Well)
(I Live Alone)
Welcome.
- My goodness. - All right.
Dae Ho, the trailer startled me so much.
- Why? - You've built...
- a theme park in your place. - Like Kangwon Land.
Seriously. I was so surprised.
I honestly want to visit your place, Dae Ho.
- Really? - I'm serious.
I'm so curious.
- It's like a rabbit hole. - Visit my place sometime.
- Your place? What... - Yes.
You'll need to wear a hazmat suit.
It'll be like entering a semiconductor factory.
You'll need to use the restroom in advance.
I have a disinfecting spray in front of the restroom.
(Don't worry.)
If you use it, you'll be clean.
It'll be safe for anyone.
(Her place is as strange as mine.)
(Dae Ho Land Opens)
- Dae Ho Land. - Dae Ho Land.
(Dae Ho comes down the mountain after hiking.)
- What? - Hey.
Hold on. Moo Do Ra Ji?
(His hiking outfit is a Moo Do Ra Ji T-shirt.)
- That's... - You know,
- the material is so good. - I picked a nice fabric.
- The material is so good. - I spent a lot of money.
He'll wear it all summer.
It's definitely summer.
We went to that place back in the day.
- We went there together. Yes. - Yes.
(At a place where he has made many memories, )
(he washes his face.)
How refreshing.
- He washed his neck too. - Nice.
- It's refreshing. - How refreshing.
Mount Inwang.
(He works out once his sweat gets cooled down.)
I haven't had a medical checkup in the last two years.
When I worked at a company, I had it regularly.
- No one takes care of you now. - No.
- You must take care of yourself. - Right.
- You're a freelancer. - Right.
Recently, I got a simple blood test...
as well as a colonoscopy.
I got "Caution" for everything.
- You got "Caution?" - I got "Caution" for everything.
You look very healthy.
I got "Caution" for my overall health.
If my daily routine collapses,
I'll use it as an excuse to get lazy.
Then my daily life will fall apart.
To prevent that, I'm working out diligently...
these days.
(As soon as he comes down from the mountain, )
My goodness.
(he begins to exercise.)
I hike.
- He is flexible. - The way he goes down tells me...
- Oh, my. - My goodness.
- He has the muscles. - On "I Am a Natural Person,"
grandpas exercise like that on a rock.
Grandpa Rock.
- Grandpa Rock. - You know what I mean, right?
- He is flexible. - Dae Ho is good with mountains.
I feel more comfortable in the mountains.
You're a mountain person.
Okay.
Let's go. I have a lot of work to do.
He lives a healthy life.
These days, I do a simple exercise...
- whenever I have time. - You take care of your health.
It's important to do that.
(Humming)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
- Okay. Hello. - He is popular in the neighborhood.
Hello.
(The neighborhood's popular man says hello to the residents.)
It's a heartwarming neighborhood.
I had just come down from the mountain.
- Hello. - My goodness.
Hello.
I'm here.
Hold on. What do I need to buy first?
It smells delicious.
- My goodness. - I love such markets.
- It has been a while. - Inwang Market.
- I see. Hongje-dong. - It's in Hongje-dong.
- It's a paradise. - Going to a market...
Once you enter such a market,
- you can't leave. - That's right.
It's a chicken place. Hello.
I haven't been to this chicken place in a while.
(It's a chicken place Dae Ho frequents.)
(He gnawed on a drumstick.)
- There is no line today. - You're right.
- There is no line. - The business is slow today.
Is the business slow today?
- It'll pick up when it gets hot. - That's right.
- I'll come and buy next time. - Okay.
I hope you sell a lot.
My goodness.
(Looking around)
What kind of fish is in season?
These days... I see.
- Seabass. - Nice.
Seabass is tasty.
- I'll eat something I want. - Hello.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
What kind of seafood is tasty these days?
- These days? Cuttlefish. - Flounder.
Cuttlefish is in season.
- That's right. - Flounders are a good choice too.
The thing is... There is a cod too.
- Cods are tasty. - Yes.
- Would you fillet it for me? - Fillet it?
- Fillets. - I'll fillet it.
- We can fillet it. - Just the fillets.
It'll be perfect if you can fillet it.
Sir, I'll get a cuttlefish as well.
- A cuttlefish? - Yes.
I can't miss out on this as it's in season.
- You must have cuttlefish. - I was a bit torn.
- That must be so good. - It's nice and low in calories.
It's going to be good.
Eating things in season...
is the best way to take care of your body.
- Right. - Right.
There's no disease that can't be cured with food.
Right. Eating good food can keep you healthy.
But you can get diseases from food as well.
- Well... - Hold on. Was that for me?
No.
- Why look at me? - He was trying to say that to me.
That was a great line.
(You misunderstood me.)
- Have a great day. - Thank you.
- I'll come again. Bye. - Goodbye.
(He heads toward the vegetable store past the fish seafood store.)
- Hello. - Hello.
I'll get one broccoli.
- One? Right. - Yes.
I'll get some spinach as well.
(Dae Ho picks different vegetables.)
You're the one in "Unknown Legend," right?
Yes. You're right.
- Right. - The MC of "Unknown Legend."
Your face is so small.
- It looked much bigger on TV. - What do you mean? It's small.
(Happy to see him)
When is the next shoot?
- The final is tomorrow. - They know everyone on the show.
They know everyone.
There are a lot of people who notice me in the market.
- Right. - Your popularity in the market...
goes up by 200 percent when you're in a trot show.
Are you connected with this store?
- Sorry? - Are you connected?
No. I live right here.
"Are you connected with this store?"
- I live in Ant Village. - That was a great question.
I came to buy some vegetables.
- I see. - Right. What are you going to get?
- I need some vegetables. - Vegetables?
I want to see Jang Min Ho as well. Why didn't you bring him?
How would I bring him here?
(They're hilarious.)
They always say things out of nowhere.
"Tell Lim Young Woong to come to my house."
"Tell him that I voted for him via text message."
- Kim Dae Ho! - Oh, hello.
- It's great to see you! - Thank you. Bye.
- Bye. - Thank you.
(Peeking)
- Hello. - Gosh, you look great.
- Thank you. - You look great in person.
- Have a great day. - You're the MC, right?
- I'm on that one as well. - Right.
Gosh, you're loved by everyone in the market!
- Do you support anyone? - It's you.
- Me? - I watch I Live Alone as well.
Gosh, thank you!
- Thank you! - You're the Market Prince.
Have a great day.
- Hello! - Hello.
(The Prince's fan meeting continues outside.)
- Where are you from? - Don't you live in Ant Village?
- Right. Do you still live there? - Right.
I still live there. It has been around eight years.
Right.
Gosh, it's great to see you.
They're dressed so nicely.
- Spring has come. - They look lovely.
You're dressed so nicely.
Was it to match the great weather?
(Acting cute)
This is my neighborhood.
I wanted to cook a meal for myself as it was my day off.
- Have a great meal. - Thank you.
(The fan meeting comes to an end.)
Hello.
Your market popularity has gone up so high.
I didn't expect that many people would come to me.
That's insane.
When you go to the market, trot shows are playing everywhere.
- Right. - They're watched in every store.
Ji Hyeon must be the king there.
- He's the king. - He's the king.
- So many people love him. - He's the most popular.
I went to Gangwon Province with him for another show.
- We weren't able to move around. - You can't move around.
- It was impossible. - Right.
I took a picture with Ji Hyeon...
and there were over 200 comments on the post.
- Of course. - Of course.
So that's why Hyun Moo treats Ji Hyeon so well.
It's completely different with how he treats him.
Gosh, the Moo Do Ra Ji.
(Dae Ho leaves the market after bringing up his popularity.)
I'll add the tomatoes.
(Whistling)
Here it is.
I wonder if I'll find all of the tools.
Gosh, it's been so long since I've seen a hardware store.
It's a really old hardware store.
Gosh, those places have everything.
- Hello. - Oh, hello.
I'm here to buy some screw nails.
- Screw nails? - Right. We have them.
- Screw nails and... - He looks so friendly.
He's stylish.
I'm looking for long ones.
How long?
- Around this long. - Right.
What are they for?
- Well... - This one?
- Yes! You're right! - Right.
He found it right away.
How is he able to find things so easily there?
- I wonder the same thing. - All owners are like that.
- That's what fascinates me. - I need a lot of these.
- How many? - Do you sell them in packets?
- We do. - I'll take a whole packet.
- I need around... - There are hundreds of them...
in one packet.
- I need around two packets. - Gosh, why do you need so many?
- What? - I needed a lot.
Even when one packet has hundreds of them?
- I need these as well. Hinges. - Yes?
- I'll be using them... - Right.
- at home. - Right.
Let's see.
(Let's see.)
- These should work. - Right.
- As for these... - Right.
Why does he need so many?
- Exactly. - I need a lot of them.
It was something I've kept pushing back to do.
- Can I use this to count them? - Yes.
I'll use this.
It's to make sure as I'll be buying a lot.
One, two, three,
four, five...
Nine, ten.
Twenty-eight, twenty-nine, thirty.
This is how many I'll need.
- I'll get 30 of these. - Right.
- And the long screw nails. - Those.
The long ones. I'll get two packets of these.
- I think that will do. - Right.
- I'll pay for these. - Right.
All of that will be...
How many of these were there again? Were there 30 of them?
Right. There were 30 of them.
There were 30.
- Am I right? - You counted them just now.
Right.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- He looks out of it. - Right.
I forgot.
(Laughing)
- One... - Elders chuckle all the time,
- but they're aware of everything. - He remembers everything.
Of course. He checked while chuckling.
(Nodding out of support)
- Gosh. - There were 30 of them.
Right. I counted it by myself, but I forgot it.
- He was watching everything. - He's so cute.
Bring them back if you don't need all of them.
There are so many of them.
- I'll need them. - What will you do with this many?
Hold on.
- There are 300 of them. - Right. There are 300 of them.
- Gosh. - You got 2 packets of 300 pieces?
- I got 600 pieces. - You got 600 pieces?
- Gosh. - Right.
There aren't many who buy this many, right?
- There aren't many. - Right.
Two packets of these...
- cost 26 dollars. - Right.
- This is 6 dollars. - Right.
So that's 32 dollars in total?
- Right. - Okay. It's 32 dollars.
They are quick at making calculations as well.
They calculate things with their heads right away.
How much was it again? Was it 32 dollars?
It's 32 dollars.
- It's 32 dollars. - Right.
I forget things easily.
Dae Ho seems to forget things too easily.
- Hold on. It seems quite serious. - Well,
I didn't want to make a single mistake...
- with the calculations. - You were worried about that?
When you sent in your letter of resignation,
you must have handed in something else as well.
- Something else was sent. - Something else was sent.
His memory cells.
I've sent it to you.
- Right. - Right.
- Goodbye. - Goodbye!
He was so friendly.
It made my day.
Will it be there?
(Dae Ho heads somewhere else.)
I'm sure they'll have enough.
(Community center)
- Community center? - Why the community center?
- Hello. - Hello.
I'm here to borrow a tool.
- I see. - A tool?
You can borrow tools from community centers.
- Right. - Really?
There it is. I remember that I saw it before.
Which tool do you need?
I need the drill.
(Dae Ho came to borrow a tool for free at the community center.)
There are so many of them as well.
There's no need for people to buy every single tool.
- Right. - As that would be a waste of money,
community centers lend them for free.
When you buy a tool, it won't be used much after one use.
- Right. - Right.
If you bring things like your ID card,
you can fill in the application form.
If you look here,
- There they are. - there are two types of drills.
- Right. - There's the one for concrete...
and the one for wood.
Which one do you need?
(Spinning)
I think this will do.
- Will you take that one? - Yes.
- This one. - Right.
I'll take the screwdriver as well.
Okay.
- I'll take these. - Would you like those two?
- Yes. - They would cost so much...
for just a single use.
This is a great system.
Thank you. I'll use them carefully and bring them back.
- Goodbye. - Thank you.
(Panting)
Gosh. Then...
(He arrives home after climbing the steep hill.)
Let's come down with the things.
(Struggling)
(He walks over to House 2.)
Gosh, let's see.
The sand is still there.
(The final stage of Dae Ho's fantasy)
(Daeundea)
I should give it some water.
Let's see.
The vivariums!
(Dad is here.)
(Dae Ho's long-time hobby and source of joy)
- You made them yourself, right? - Yes.
(Feeling proud)
You did well to take care of them. Having more time to yourself...
- definitely helped. - That helped a lot.
Have you been doing well?
- Gosh! - What is that?
- The waxy monkey. - You know, don't you?
- I knew he would know. - The waxy monkey.
To maintain its moisture,
- wax comes out from its body. - Right.
That is why it's called that.
It's called the monkey...
because it crawls around like a monkey.
- It hangs around. - Right.
I'm very interested in these creatures as well.
- I even went to an exposition. - Gosh.
Here's a new member for Dae Ja Yeon.
I love these things.
(His eyes are full of love.)
I'll spray you with some water.
(Spraying)
(Feeling refreshed)
- Gosh. - Right. It must be kept...
in the right humidity and temperature.
"Gosh, this feels great."
(After a therapeutic time, )
(he remembers to provide more water.)
Great.
I'll come back later at night.
(I'll come back later.)
- Those are judo mats. - Right.
They're hard to purchase as they're for gyms.
You would never find those at someone's home.
(Mats found at gyms)
Here we go.
(Lifting)
(He brings out the mats from House 2.)
What will you be doing with those now?
(They're moved to House 1.)
(Let's head inside first.)
(Sliding open)
- What? - That was your bedroom.
- You're not moving out, are you? - I'm not.
Just like how seasons change, I wanted to bring some change.
My health was getting worse...
and my daily life was collapsing.
But this cycle kept repeating.
I decided to make a fresh change while I was at it.
I wiped out everything as if I just moved in.
(The house was emptied to look like a new house.)
It's completely clean!
- Did you get rid of everything? - I got rid of everything.
I got rid of my clothes as well.
It's go big or go home for Dae Ho.
(Emptiness therapy for his health)
(Neat)
He wiped out everything.
- Right. - That's amazing.
(He brings in the mats he brought from House 2.)
What will he be doing...
- with the mats? - I wonder.
(He manages to bring them all in.)
Come here, Nana.
Nana!
I'll make a playground for you.
It's Nana.
(Wait for just a while.)
There's no time to waste.
What is he doing?
I wonder what he's going to do.
(Heave-ho!)
I was planning to install the steppers.
(I was planning to install the steppers.)
(A couple of them were on the wall.)
(Na Ra...)
(and Ja Yeon had them at their homes as well.)
(Cat steppers)
- For the cat. - I see.
It's for the cat.
Cats love going up.
They want to go up here and there.
I thought it would be a good idea...
to install the steppers for the cat.
We do have a cat tower at home,
but I wanted the cat to move around the whole house.
I decided to make an area...
for Nana Land.
That was why you bought a lot of hinges.
How many of steppers will be for him to need 300 screw nails?
He bought 600!
- Right. He bought 600. - Right.
Will you be living on the cat tower as well?
You won't be sleeping there, right?
- I sleep there with my cat. - Really? Gosh.
Let's see.
(I'll try to be quick, Nana.)
One should be installed here.
Cats can tell even if something is slightly slanted.
He won't go up if it feels uncomfortable.
(It's at the right level.)
(The nail is ready.)
(Shall I begin?)
(Drilling)
(Stuck)
What's wrong?
It's too weak.
The nail spins in place if the drill is too weak.
Gosh.
I can't do this with a screwdriver.
(He tries again with the screwdriver.)
(Struggling)
This won't work.
(I have so many of them to install.)
(I can't do this with just my hands.)
(Giving up)
(What do I do?)
You can't do it with your hands if the drill won't work.
Right.
Gosh.
(What will you do?)
I think I kept it somewhere here.
It's low on batteries.
Here it is.
It worked with this.
I had the tool at home,
but it was low on batteries.
I couldn't find the charger for it.
Gosh!
I tried using the tool at home.
(He tries again with his own drill.)
Gosh, it's working well.
- It worked right away. - Right.
(Drilling in)
- It went right in. - Okay!
There we go.
I'm finally making progress.
Nana! Give me a moment.
I'll make you the best place for you.
Okay!
He'll love it.
It's Nana's house anyway.
(Tearing)
(He places the mats as well.)
The mats.
- In case the cat falls off? - Okay.
So that he doesn't have to jump straight down to the ground.
Right.
(Walking over)
He's loving it.
Do you like it, Nana? It's nice and soft, isn't it?
He still loves it.
He must like it.
All right.
Safety always comes first.
(He checks the cushion by jumping on it.)
Nana!
This must be fine.
Okay.
What was that?
- He fell down like that. - He dropped down all of a sudden.
I just wanted to check.
Great.
I've made your playground. I'll work on mine now.
(I've made your playground. I'll work on mine now.)
What is that?
(Rattling)
Whatever.
- What? - What are those?
(Surprised)
- What are those? - What?
You'll be doing that at home?
(What are you doing?)
I've made your playground. I'll work on mine now.
(He moves busily after finishing with the steppers.)
Whatever.
(Pouring out)
- What? - What are those?
Today,
I will be working on another big project...
like the one for Daeundae.
It's Nana Land, but it's also my place.
I'm planning to create a wall climbing area.
You'll be installing those on the wall?
I don't work out often,
but there was something that I did as a hobby.
That was climbing.
There aren't that many indoor climbing centers in Korea.
I see.
(Various holds are installed on the wall...)
(in indoor climbing centers.)
(What?)
- Ja Yeon. - I see!
You wanted to share the same hobby with her!
I see.
- Gosh! - You're trying to...
bring back that connection?
(The connection with Ja Yeon)
So climbing will be the spark of that?
- He wants to be with Ja Yeon? - No.
- We got you. - He wants to be with Ja Yeon.
It was a coincidence.
Gosh, I got goosebumps all over.
- Oh, come on. - Check out his plan.
I've always enjoyed climbing.
You're creeping me out.
That's a crazy plan.
(Actually, whenever he saw a rock wall...)
- Gosh. - I keep holding on to those.
From here...
(Dae Ho worked on his grip whenever he could.)
I thought it would be exciting to make a climbing area at home.
I've always had that dream.
It will start from the living room to the small window.
You have to fulfill the dream you had.
There's excitement when you learn.
There are so many things that can make you feel excited,
but the moment that brings the most excitement...
is to do something you wanted to do whenever you want to.
It would be hard to do...
if I thought about the house,
but my overall health was at the warning level.
My personal motto is to live while cleaning my mess.
That was why I decided to make it happen first.
"Let's give it a try as it's my house anyway."
You can do anything you want at your house.
Okay.
(He places the hold on the wall.)
(Drilling)
Okay.
Can those stay on the wall?
That was why I bought screw nails.
(Fixed with sturdy screw nails)
(Shall I check if it's safe by hanging on it?)
(Arms shaking)
Okay!
There we go.
I should start with the big pieces.
I can't believe I'm doing this at home.
(Touched)
He's loving it like a young boy.
(He's loving it like a young boy.)
(His dream becomes reality with each piece.)
The ceiling isn't that high up.
That's why it's even better.
This is amazing.
It's a real deal if you install them on the ceiling.
(Grabbing)
Gosh, hanging there?
That's for real experts.
(Drilling into the ceiling)
Okay.
All right.
(Dae Ho's climbing gym is taking shape.)
(Shall I give it a try?)
It works!
Gosh, it works.
He's amazing.
(He successfully lifted himself from the floor.)
It works.
- He's so happy. - That way...
The thing that I only imagined actually came true.
That's when you feel the happiest.
Gosh, this works? All right.
(Deeply moved)
The house is shaped like an indoor climbing gym.
The house has bumps and dips here and there.
The bumps act as climbing holds.
Climbing comes in many forms like bouldering.
There's also speed climbing.
Actually, I'm just a beginner,
so I'd just install lots of holds...
to make my own routes from them.
That's what I'm trying to do.
- But what about the steps... - Didn't you install that for Nana?
You installed for Nana?
That's where it's more difficult.
- I see. You did it on purpose. - Yes, I did.
Maybe you'll be climbing the walls when we visit.
- That's why I installed them. - In the end, you became a lizard.
- You became a lizard in the end. - You became a lizard yourself.
Afterward, you'll jump into the vivarium.
You'll stay in the vivarium with the others.
With the waxy monkey frog.
(The whole house is the playground for Dae Ho the lizard.)
(Daezard is working hard.)
(Halting)
Darn. Is the battery done?
- Oh, it's out of battery. - Oh, no. You need to charge it.
That's why I didn't use that from the start.
(It ran out of battery in the end.)
(Gosh, what do I do?)
What do I do?
I'm done for the day.
No!
No.
Oh, my goodness.
I must run in case they close.
(I must run in case they close.)
Is this Fun Run or something? What is this?
This is like Fun Run.
(He's running at the Fun Run pace seamlessly.)
(Panting)
It's not closed.
I went to the hardware store...
- where you can pay and borrow. - Hello.
- Oh, a hardware store. - I...
This one ran out of battery.
Okay.
- Is this one? - That's the one.
That's the same one.
I'll borrow that one.
Thank you. How much is it?
- It's 20 dollars for rent. - It's 20 dollars?
- That's why I went... - Really?
- to the community center. - Oh, it's free there.
Yes.
(Rummaging)
(Wait.)
What?
(What?)
Sir, I left my phone.
- I left my phone. - Gosh.
- I'll wire it to you. - Put it on your tab.
Why don't you trust me... I'll leave this here.
I haven't seen anyone putting it on their tab for a long time.
- This is... - Do you know "Unknown Legend?"
It's a TV show.
(I'm not a weird man.)
Or could I leave my ID here?
Should I? Okay, thank you.
It's my driver's license.
- I'll come back for it tomorrow. - What's your phone number?
It's 010... I've been here before.
That's me, Kim Dae Ho.
Actually, he has my number on his phone...
because I've been there before.
Gosh, thank you, sir.
I'll just leave this here too.
Yes. Thank you.
Thank goodness.
(He could've come back again. It's a relief.)
I'm so glad.
I can do it!
I can do it.
(He starts running after cheering himself up.)
I can do this.
I think you're running more than I did in Gangwon Province.
He ran way more.
- Running with tools. - Running with tools.
I can do it.
(Sighing)
I should charge it first.
(Charging the battery that ran out)
That's it.
(Taking it)
All right.
(The drill from the hardware store is working fine.)
It's ready.
I can't hold out anymore. I haven't eaten anything today.
I should eat something first.
(Eat before you get back to work.)
I should eat as simply as possible.
(Washing the vegetables he got from the market thoroughly)
Putting it in.
(Blanching the vegetables he washed cleanly)
(Adding olive oil)
(Adding the blanched vegetables)
- I cooked it in advance. - Right, gently stir-fry it.
(Golden brown)
(Drizzling olive oil into the air fryer)
(Adding the onions he cut...)
Gosh, it's onions.
(and salted butter)
(Scoring the plump codfish)
It's deboned.
- The grain is like this. - Right.
If you cut it vertically, the meat gets cut off easily,
so it's convenient to eat.
- It's cuttlefish! It looks so good. - It's like he's camping.
Fatsia shoot.
(Covering it with vegetables that are in golden brown)
It's a Western-style steamed dish.
- That's right. - Yes.
You cook so easily without measuring.
- He's good at cooking, so... - Dae Ho's foods are really good.
(Covering the air fryer cover well)
I'm cooking it with an air fryer right away.
Let's cook it for 20 minutes.
Start.
(All he has to do is wait for 20 minutes!)
All right.
(The food is getting cooked deliciously.)
I'm hungry.
(He finally has his first meal of the day.)
Goodness.
Dishes like papillote are served at wine stores.
- Papillote? - Yes.
Hold on. The codfish meat.
(He blows on it after scooping it with a rice paddle.)
(Taking a big bite)
(Thrilled)
It's so moist.
It was so moist. It was good.
I can't believe I made this at home.
(This time, he grabs the whole cuttlefish.)
(He takes a bite right away.)
(Yes, this is it.)
It's so moist.
It's not fried at all.
It'll be so good if you add glass noodles there.
You want to add glass noodles to that dish too?
(Placing it 1 by 1 on the rice paddle)
(Showing off his towering skill)
(Slurping it skillfully)
It must be good.
(Happy)
I should eat the rest later. I can heat it up.
- I'll just close it. - The best part about it...
is you can put it in the fridge as is since it has a cover.
- It's convenient. - I'll leave it here for now.
Shall I wrap up now?
(He resumes working.)
All right.
(Even on the pillar connecting the living room and the bedroom, )
(he skillfully installs holds.)
He installs them everywhere.
(Smiling widely)
(Laughing)
I get the kind of happiness he feels.
And it was...
- taking shape eventually. - Right.
(Smiling)
Dae Ho also has a hint of madness.
(Only one hold remains now.)
(If I install just this, )
(it'll be done for real.)
I was so happy.
(Grunting)
(I'm finally done.)
All right.
(Let's see.)
Let me see.
- You feel proud, don't you? - I was really happy.
(I'm going to make an indoor climbing gym.)
(He installed his dream on the white wall all day...)
(in order to become healthy.)
(He's done making his own indoor climbing gym.)
He's gone crazy for real.
At first, I thought it was reckless.
- But now that I'm seeing this, - It's good, right?
- I want to go and try it. - It's not bad, right?
I do want to try climbing.
I want to go right now.
(Impressed)
It's fantastic.
I've always dreamed of it, but it came true.
The indoor climbing gym...
is the highest for me. It's Mount Deverest.
- Mount Deverest. - It really is okay.
Everyone, come conquer it.
I want to go to Mount Deverest.
(Bringing something over)
I didn't do it half-heartedly.
- You have specialized tools too? - You have tools like that too?
Of course I do. I actually did rock climbing before.
I did it for a year.
Then that makes sense.
It's Mount Deverest.
(It's as good as Mount Everest in Nepal.)
(Mount Deverest of Hongje-dong)
I'm going to climb this today...
without failing it once.
Why are you putting that on when you're just climbing your wall?
It's even more upsetting that you've put on the ropes.
You like it because it feels like...
- you're doing it in earnest. - Of course.
I wanted to live out my dream.
- That's why I put on the tools. - I totally get what you mean.
- Why didn't you put on chalk? - Sorry?
- They have a chalk bag. - This one.
- Because the house becomes messy. - That's right.
- You mind that too? - He did everything to mess it up.
Were you going to put it on if it didn't make your house messy?
(Putting on the shoes for climbing)
(Putting on cotton work gloves instead of chalk...)
(to keep the house clean)
(Let's go!)
(He's perfectly ready from head to toe.)
I'm curious. I want to see him finish until the end.
Reaching the other side after turning around.
(Tapping)
(Checking the hold)
Let's go!
- Be careful. - You have to be careful.
(He starts climbing Mount Deverest.)
(Placing)
This actually works.
(Amazed)
I'm telling you, it does.
Of course it does.
(Placing his head)
(Glancing)
Normally, you plan before installing holds.
It felt like I was figuring out the quest as I went on.
- I see. - That's right.
It's a really difficult course, though.
(His body starts to ache in no time.)
(Quickly searching for the next hold)
I knew this would happen.
He didn't even take that many steps.
Why are you doing slapstick comedy on a variety show?
- That came off. - That came off.
(He fell after the hold on his foot came off.)
Come back to your senses!
But I was really thrilled then.
Everyone around me was against it...
because the wall...
- was made of drywall. - That's right.
They said it wouldn't work,
but when I went on it,
- it worked. - When it works...
- I was really excited. - It gives you a thrill.
- Yes. - That's right.
I feel like it'll work.
- Give it one more try. - Yes, you should.
- You need to conquer it! - Yes.
You must conquer it.
(Visualizing the route in his head)
I can do this.
Let's go, Moo Do Ra Ji.
You can do it.
(He tries climbing Mount Deverest again.)
Can you take off my T-shirt before you go?
- Why? - It's embarrassing me too.
(Joking)
(He continues climbing without caring.)
(Holding)
- All right. That's good. - He's leaning.
- That's it! - That's good.
(He barely manages to turn his body.)
He's gone pretty far.
Yes.
Move. Go to the kitchen.
It's really hard to go from there.
That part looks hard, obviously.
You need to be flexible.
Grab this, and...
(If I go a little further, I'll reach the bedroom.)
Please!
(Slipping)
(Stepping)
(He saved himself with his quick feet.)
(Groaning)
(Panting)
(The next target)
(Cracking)
Why you... You crazy punk!
He's a crazy punk!
Mister.
Hyun Moo, he's crazy.
(Hyun Moo is about to go crazy too.)
Nana hasn't even used it yet.
(Chuckling bitterly)
- I'm so stressed out right now. - Dae Ho has gone crazy.
What are you doing? It got hit by your belly and broke.
(Bulging)
But it must feel like...
- doing rock climbing. - It does.
- A rock fell too. - For real.
Did you hear the sound? It sounded like a rock falling.
(It's perfect.)
(Snapping)
I'm so sick of him.
(Nana's wall step fell after getting hit by Dae Ho's belly.)
I'm sorry.
Nana, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'll fix it later.
(Screaming)
Nana, I'm sorry.
(I'd rather not watch.)
Did the heat get to him?
(Crying)
Nana, I'm sorry.
(Laughing)
(The step fell too.)
Darn it, I was almost there.
(Dae Ho fell too.)
If it wasn't for the hold...
(Crying)
I could've made it...
- if it wasn't for that hold. - I made it through the hard part.
Don't explain it to me.
Nana.
- Nana left, of course. - Darn, they all broke.
Gosh, this is ridiculous.
(He sets off again after soothing his broken heart.)
This part is super difficult.
Will I be able to do it?
If I fall from here, my head will crack.
(The path Dae Ho has to take)
(After passing the floor without the mat...)
Right. There's no mat there.
It'll be so thrilling if there's no mat.
The mats were more expensive than I thought.
- Right. - So I only got four for now.
You traded it for your life.
(He can only finish after climbing one more side.)
Okay.
(Finish line)
It's a really difficult part.
- Try going to the next room. - I should, yes.
I want to see him go to the next room too.
He went through so much to install them.
(He struggles to climb the wall.)
All right, he got it. He's in.
Let's go.
(Looking around)
Which one? Which one should I step on?
(Lost)
One might think it's a horror movie.
(Let's just go for now.)
- I need to grab the one on top. - Yes.
(Here we go!)
Gosh, what do I do?
Seriously, what's wrong with you?
I have to make a turn.
(Dae Ho is doing climbing in his house.)
- I need to grab the one on top. - Yes.
(He moves his feet, relying on his arm strength.)
(Grunting)
- Why on earth are you doing that? - Well, that was...
- He's gone completely crazy. - Crazy?
- He's gone crazy. - He's crazy.
- What are you doing? - What's wrong with you?
Is becoming a monkey your dream?
(Worried)
But seriously... Dae Ho, you're okay, right?
- I'm okay. - Okay.
- I'm really happy. - The back of your head is okay?
- It's okay. - I see.
You're not a monkey.
Dae Ho is getting weirder and weirder.
Why don't you install an electrified floor system next time?
Or stand nails upright on the floor.
It's more thrilling if you lose something when you fall.
- Should I bring a shark? - Right. Anything will be good.
Okay. I can do it.
I'm almost done.
(He pulls himself up while cheering for himself.)
It must be a great workout. You're sweating a lot.
It's... It's like lifting your own weight.
Okay, let's go.
Hold on.
(He tries to enter the bedroom again.)
Gosh, I got a cramp.
- Gosh, seriously... - Oh, my.
(Shaking)
My goodness.
(Numb)
(He gets out of the cramp for a second.)
All right. This and that.
I was going to go quickly before I got the cramp again.
Gosh, hold on. I got a cramp again.
You got it again?
(He even got a cramp in his butt.)
- What are you doing? - I mean...
How do I ease it?
I didn't know how to ease the cramp.
Personally, I wish your mother wouldn't watch this.
Your mother will start doing early morning prayers.
- She could cry. - Early morning prayers?
But I couldn't just go down. I couldn't give up.
You could go down.
- But... - But he's already up there,
- so he'd want to see it through. - That's right.
He invested so much time installing them.
(His butt is still shaking in pain.)
You're quite sexy.
Until when will he shake his butt? I don't want to see it.
What do I do?
(Why did I get a cramp in my butt?)
(Get it together!)
If you fall, you die! Just think that you'll die.
- "If you fall, you die." - It's the edge of the cliff.
From here...
I used to play like that a lot...
- when I was young. - That's right.
I'd always play barefoot and go up like that at my grandma's place.
- That's right. - If you fall, you die.
I always kept that in mind.
- That's right. - That's right.
That means you're still at that age mentally.
The boy is still living in him.
- The boy. - The boyish charm.
(The boy is losing strength in his arm.)
Grab that and...
(Grabbing)
Grab this too.
- Go at once. - One, two, go.
That's it.
(Slipping)
I haven't fallen.
(I haven't fallen.)
- What? You fell. - No, I didn't fall.
- What was that? - I didn't fall.
(Struggling)
How do I go from here?
(Flailing)
He's playing escape room by himself.
(He got another life, but it's not easy to go forward.)
Gosh, he's having so much fun.
(Chuckling)
(He's not sure if he's laughing or crying.)
Let's go back!
(Unable to move)
(In the end, he falls off the cliff.)
He died.
I died.
(Crying)
I can't cross this part.
I was really tired then.
(Exhausted)
Oh, no.
(Groaning)
I'm having cramps.
(Fortunately, he can still feel his leg.)
I got cramps.
(Save me.)
I can do it. Hold on.
Still... Hold on. I should do this.
(Getting up)
(He suddenly revived.)
- You didn't give up. - No.
Okay.
(Giving another try for the dream he didn't fulfill)
Okay, I got it.
Great. Great posture. This is it.
(Back in reform after he revived)
(Grabbing without hesitation)
Oh, no!
- Grab that. - That's it.
(But he overcame the crisis.)
Taking that one step wasn't easy.
(Only if I pass this part...)
(Taking each step slowly)
If you finish it, it gives you a great sense of achievement.
Yes.
(It's his last step already.)
Yes, do it until the end. He's almost there.
- You're almost there. - He's almost there.
(He finally managed to climb Mount Deverest.)
(I made it!)
(He rummages through something right away?)
- What is it? - What's that?
What is it?
There must be something. He's doing something.
- It's my true dream. - Oh, really?
- You're hanging yourself there. - Oh, to do that?
(Going down)
(Hanging just like that)
Nana?
- Is it Churu? - Is it his snack?
- Nana's snack. - Nana?
Nana.
Let's have this.
Come here.
(He managed to lure him with a snack.)
(Thinking)
Come up here.
That's it.
(Jumping)
Nana, come here.
- Come here. - You wanted to be with him.
That's it.
I wanted to do this with you.
He's having a beer.
Alcohol is not allowed in the mountains,
- so it's a raisin tree tea. - Right.
- A raisin tree tea? - Yes, a raisin tree tea.
A raisin tree tea.
(Enjoying the climb with a refreshing raisin tree tea)
It's not coming out because the can was squeezed, right?
- Because I fell... - Right?
- It didn't come out. - The can is a bit...
(Even though the tea didn't come out well...)
Nice view.
Dae Ho is really imaginative.
Next time, you should put on...
- VR goggles next time. - That's right.
- The VR for cliffs. - That's right.
(That sounds like a good idea.)
When I reached the finish line,
there was something I wanted to do.
That was just me hanging without relying on a hold...
and enjoying a happy moment with Nana.
Fulfilling your own dream is really...
(Sharing a happy moment with Nana)
It only takes five steps to get there.
But I used an hour to climb.
(Laughing)
Still, I'm glad I reached the end. I'm so proud of it.
I fell after two steps,
but I took three steps after overcoming it.
Turning the corner and reaching the end.
The thrill it gave me was incredible.
I think my place's climbing route isn't so bad.
I'll turn it into an indoor climbing gym,
so anyone can come.
I'll provide drinks too.
(Considering)
I'm torn between wanting to go and not wanting to go.
- I'm still contemplating. - You keep debating, right?
He's a competitive type.
- But I do want to give it a try. - You want to try going once?
- Right? - I was moved.
- Dae Ho lives the happiest. - Seriously. He's the best.
You must do whatever you want.
You hold on to romance in your heart to the very end.
- I wanted to try it. - That's amazing.
(After enjoying the view fully...)
(Falling)
(1 hour of romance was sweet.)
You're still not defeated by time.
(A Life in Pursuit of Romance)
(Next story)
(My shoes were in the living room.)
(The living room is a mess.)
(Moomoo's house was robbed?)
You little punk.
(Moomoo's good son project)
(Part 2)
(He gave the lucky dog...)
(to his parents instead of a grandchild.)
(A new family member he brought from a difficult environment)
(A baby dog who's only 70 days old)
(What should I name you?)
(Snowy)
(Yeolmu)
(Baekseolgi)
(I don't like them at all!)
(Should I name you this?)
(It's no different from raising a child.)
(Biting)
(Save Fathermoo!)
(No.)
(Come here.)
(You can't eat that.)
(I can't go on anymore.)
(Old Fathermoo is out of energy.)
(Fathermoo's Parenting Diary)
What is this? What do I do?
(Kang Yong is finally moving.)
(Even getting a deposit loan is already a struggle.)
(He checks out houses without giving up.)
(It wasn't easy...)
(to look for a new house.)
(The day of moving, leaving the house he cherished)
(He finally found his dream house.)
(Kang Yong's new house with the best location)
(He borrowed as much as 120,000 dollars.)
(The new house is nice.)
When will I finish organizing?
(Sighing)
(Why does it come down by itself?)
(Something's gone wrong with the upper cabinet.)
(Why is it so hard...)
(to get to the dining table?)
(On top of everything else, the power went out?)
(Crying)
(It's dark.)
(I miss Mom.)
(I Need to Become Stronger)